Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
Aiming to defeat Lit, leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun, Asta and his fellow royal knights stormed his floating fortress.
Their attack seemed to overwhelm the enemy at first, until...
Seriously, why are we here?
Did I say you could duplicate yourself?
Hey, it's not like the heavy choice it is!
Whatever, you're obviously the fake one!
You're the fake one and you know it!
Stop yelling!
That's one solution.
What's wrong with you? You could've killed me!
You survived a trial by fire, and I wouldn't have brought anyone who couldn't.
The imposter was none other than Raya the Disloyal, last remaining member of the Third Eye.
I'll show you what destruction looks like!
Flame magic!
Kalingos Brachium!
Thus began a fierce battle between the powers of flame magic and copy magic.
As the fight raged on, the ferocity of Meraleona's attack spells got the better of Raya.
Nearby, Yuno's team approached the center of the fortress.
Aaaaah!
Sorry, but you can't defeat me. You don't have what it takes.
Do you hear that?
I heard it before, too.
A heartbeat.
The mana here feels so... familiar.
Meanwhile, the Black Bulls celebrate a narrow victory after a surprise attack by the Midnight Sun.
We-we managed to fend them off somehow, but what are we supposed to do now that our hideout is in ruins?
We won't be inviting those guests back again.
Um, Henry? Are you absolutely sure that you can't fix the hideout?
Not now. My magic's all spent.
What are we going to do, Ghosh?
I'm not doing anything until I find my Marie treasures! Now where do they go?!
Crushed to bits, I bet. In tiny little pieces.
If you're gonna piss me off, at least hurry it up!
And while you're at it, get down here and help me, would you?
You sure?
Get your big, slow-talking mop head off that wall right now!
Um, Ghosh? Wait!
I wouldn't recommend that, actually.
Hurry up!
You know...
Whatever it is, I don't care! Get down here!
Okie-dokie...
Was that so hard, you-
When Henry gets too close to someone, he sucks all of their power away!
I tried to warn you, Ghosh.
I found it!
Thank goodness you're safe.
And look, there's not a scratch on you, not even a speck of-
Huh?
You've been tainted!
I'll kill them all!
The Eye of the Midnight Sun is dead!
How are you gonna do that? They're all gone.
Shut up, or I'll kill you while I'm at it!
I'll behave...
Give me my magic back!
Nope...
Can't...
What the heck is that supposed to mean?!
I... can't...
I'm worried, though.
The Eye of the Midnight Sun said they came here looking for something, remember?
But we still don't know what that is, or what it might do!
Probably just a bluff.
The only thing here that's worth anything is my Marie memorabilia.
You don't think they were coming from my dolls?
I don't think so, guys.
Well, if there was something valuable here, then it must be...
What do you mean?
What was it mean?
Forget it, alright?
Whatever this is about, Captain Yami can figure it out once he finally decides to come back.
I hope so!
Such unlucky timing, too.
Don't let the place get overrun by robbers, he said.
Is he psychic?
What was it mean?!
Something like that.
Should it run into town and do something?
Apass that is not what we can actually do somewhere that you can't scriptures if someone can create a treasure,
It doesn't depend on many people who willяли those things.
I willorfano away!
Did you even have a Lage that you can bring in your hands alone?
To you lose the challenge of this,ключon?
And I can дерев'eara's addiction.
Use your pocket the fatto of photography.
You have to be saved as a Uncle Pine Frog game himself!
Oh no, I will playintegrate some damage to you on the Katie trouvé!
Yes
The Dead is running Allah's slower
I will jump back!
I'm happy now doing it.
But it's hard to run Wardano utilis I won't turn my mind
I'll see you next time.
What are you losers gawkin' at?
Yummy, sir.
That's me.
Would you like some more tea, perhaps?
More tea?
Are you trying to drown me in this stuff or what?
Do you know how many times I've had to go to the bathroom today?
It's gonna start pouring out of my ears any minute now.
And by the way, is this some kind of herbal bullcrap?
Because it tastes like I've got a pine tree in my mouth.
We're very sorry, sir.
I thought old Goldie Guts called me here to apologize.
What's the big idea making me wait around all day?
How much longer is this gonna take?
I'm sure that he'll be here as soon as possible.
Here's some tea in the meantime.
No, thanks.
Almost had me there.
I bet you think you're clever.
Not at all, sir.
You know, a ride's out of commission at the moment,
so it wasn't exactly convenient to drag my butt all the way out here.
I'll be frank.
I know selection exam battles can get pretty intense,
but that vice-captain of yours was off the rails.
He busted up Finral like nobody's business.
In fact, he's still in the hospital now, knocked out cold.
As you've likely heard, they hauled your boy in for questioning,
but that's going nowhere fast.
If he had any manners, it seems to me your captain would have come to my place
rather than keeping me waiting all day.
You playing me for a fool, Golden Dawn?
He's out for blood.
We simply cannot apologize enough for the way that vice-captain Longris behaved.
That aside, I assure you that Captain Vongens is trustworthy.
He's a man of tremendous integrity as well.
Whatever his reason for making you wait,
I know he would never be intentionally discourteous.
Okay, who the hell are you?
I'm not an enemy!
You say you're not, but you look pretty shady in that peacock costume of yours.
Yami, I believe your name was.
Watch my back, if you would.
This guy...
He moves like he's able to read my mind or something.
Our key must be on the same wavelength.
How many years has it been since then?
We both became squad captains together.
Well, I'm the kind of guy who goes with his gut instinct.
Vongens, if you don't mind, lose the mask.
I understand, Yami.
You are suspicious of me, aren't you?
You think I might be the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
There's something about him that I feel in you, too.
So come on, show me your face.
My whole life, they called me a cursed child.
I'm glad I got the chance to show you who I am.
Thank you, Yami.
I didn't have any reason to doubt his sincerity.
Please, sir.
Just a bit longer.
Have faith in the captain.
Yeah, I know.
You don't gotta tell me twice.
Julius, sir.
Are you here, sir?
I need to speak with you.
I take my eyes off him for one second and he runs off.
Show some responsibility for once.
You're the Wizard King.
I'd love to complain about this pile of work he left,
but my transmission magic isn't getting through.
Right now, I'm sure the Royal Knights are fighting their final battle
with the Eye of the Midnight Sun, deep within their hideout.
Of course, I'd love to swoop in and join them,
but I've been watching them long enough
to know that they'll be fine on their own.
Their power,
and their desire to keep this nation safe
will not fail them.
I need only offer them my faith,
even from afar.
Besides, Marks would be furious if I left.
I have my own duty to attend to, after all.
Here and now.
How unusual for you to come to speak with me like this.
What's the occasion, William?
First, I must thank you for taking the time to indulge my selfish request.
From the start, you have acknowledged me for my worth,
even though my appearance is strange.
When I met you, my entire future opened up before me.
I was raised as a cursed child in a poor village,
in the Forsaken Realm.
I suffered such cruel treatment,
even from the family where I had been welcomed as the nobleman's successor.
But then...
Incredible!
What was that magic you were just using?
You showed me kindness.
You showed me respect.
You invited me to become a magic knight.
I'm serious.
Your face isn't something you ought to be ashamed of.
However, if it bothers you that much...
I'll give you this mask!
When you presented me with this gift,
when you allowed me to join your order,
and everything became certain to me,
I would dedicate my grimoire to you and your cause.
It's been 11 years,
and my sentiments haven't changed one bit.
There's no one in this world
that I respect as much as you.
Uh, yeah.
Where did all this praise come from?
How about that tournament, huh?
Bit by bit,
I climbed the ranks
until I became a magic knight captain.
Guided by my own mana,
I selected talented squad members
and created the Golden Dawn.
As thanks for the kindness you showed me,
I built the strongest squad of knights
that I could assemble.
I did that for you.
But also,
for someone else who is equally dear to me.
A friend who's always been at my side.
One I've known even longer than you.
Now, I'm faced with two loved ones
who desire two very different paths.
I'm torn between the dream that we fought for
and the dream of my dear friend.
I've known from the start
I couldn't possibly choose between you.
So now,
that decision must fall on your shoulders.
It's scars.
William, my only human friend,
I know this was hard for you.
I'm grateful.
Greetings to you,
Wizard King Julius Novakrono.
I am the leader of the Eye of the Midnight Sun.
Known as Lit.
I have dreaded this day.
Yet here we are.
William,
I knew you'd been hiding something for a long time now.
A part of you that you couldn't show to anyone,
not even me.
Yami felt the same way, I'm certain.
Perhaps Weigolion saw your true form before his defeat.
That must have come as quite a shock for him.
The day the royal capital was attacked
by the Eye of the Midnight Sun,
the profound unease I felt
when I was confronted by Licht.
I was struck by the familiar air of his mana,
and I couldn't help but notice
that you made yourself scarce
after I injured his hand.
Naturally, my suspicions began to grow.
Yet I told myself it couldn't possibly be true.
I trusted you, after all.
But now I've witnessed the truth.
You and William are not the same,
but rather two souls and one body.
In that sense,
I suppose I wasn't betrayed.
How did you get rid of the scars on your face?
It didn't seem to be magic.
The scars belong only to William,
the mark of a curse he inherited
from his mother's side of the family.
But even if I share this body,
a human's curse has nothing to do with me.
In fact, I despise humans.
William, of course,
is the sole exception.
We were able to coexist
in the same body, after all.
He may have been human,
but he accepted my feelings.
He understood me.
My boundless fury,
sorrow,
hatred,
all of it.
We're like this bird.
It's not strong,
but it can do something special.
It can fly.
As for us,
we have special magic powers
that the humans envy,
so they want to cause us pain.
Still, I think
we may be able to understand
each other better someday.
How wrong I was.
I admit I was a bit surprised.
I didn't think your brother
would feel the same way as me.
We both feel strongly about it.
I know it won't happen overnight,
but I hope elves and humans
can live in harmony.
If not,
what will we do?
Don't worry.
We're proof that it can happen, right?
Yeah.
If only I'd never met those humans.
All those lives.
There's only one way
to bring them the justice they deserve.
To quench this blazing hatred.
I will gather all the magic stones
and fulfill our ambitions at last.
So it's revenge he wants
against all humanity.
But how will he use the stones
to accomplish that?
William understood my suffering.
That's why he set up
this little meeting between us.
I believe the remaining stones
are in your possession.
We thought that would be
the safest course of action.
I will attain those stones now
and bring our hopes to fruition.
I understand.
You've always had such a kind heart.
Your dear friend is in pain
and you'd do anything
to ease his suffering,
wouldn't you, William?
But you must be suffering as well.
And just as your friend
relied on you,
you can rely on me.
I'm always on your side.
That's why I will bring an end
to this no matter what.
You may believe what you like,
but his heart and mine
are one on this matter.
Now, Wizard King,
I think it's time for you to die.
As the most powerful mage
in this nation,
you must bear its sins.
The crimes that were committed
by its people
will be paid for in your blood.
Light creation magic.
Light swords of conviction.
Monozone.
Chronostasis Gregora.
Light magic may be fast.
Faster than other magic,
certainly.
But that's not to say
there's no defense against it.
Very good.
But even that has its limits.
This man's magic
controls the flow of time,
slowing it down to a crawl
to bind someone in place,
or speeding it up
to cause ages of deterioration
instantly.
A single strike
could result in my death.
But the hand of faith
is in my favor.
I was born a wielder
of light magic after all.
And unlike any other force
in this world,
even before time,
light will not heal.
Light creation magic.
Light whip of judgment.
What's happening?
He's combining Monozone
with a spell that speeds up time
in his vicinity.
By accelerating time
for the mana surrounding him,
he can see how it's going to flow,
thereby perceiving the tiniest portion
of the future
and predicting my attacks.
Be that as it may,
I won't be overtaken so easily.
Too slow.
Even if you see into the future,
it seems that you can only
evade my attacks so quickly.
I imagine it's been quite some time
since you've suffered
an injury like that.
Very true.
Now, I've extinguished the futures
of countless people in battle,
but it's been ages
since I've seen my own blood.
Even magic that controls time itself
seems to have a limit.
Actually,
I don't control time
so much as I steal it
from my target.
This stolen time
is stockpiled bit by bit,
then used again
whenever I so please.
Though the cost
can be quite great.
He's turned back time
and healed.
I have the power
to steal the future,
but that's not my goal.
Rather,
as the Wizard King,
I hope to make a future
with no discrimination.
And I can't die
until I achieve that.
That's rich
coming from a human!
Don't make me laugh!
At this speed,
it will take all his power
just to dodge my magic.
Never mind a counterattack,
he can't even get close to me!
It's over.
His predictions are improving!
I can already see your future,
and I can assure you
it ends in defeat.
I don't need no money.
I don't need no魔力は要ない。
自力で挑んだミラクル起きること願い。
魅力ながら1ミリずつビリビリ切り込んでく。
世界を巻き込んでく。
My disability is my ability。
逆にそれが俺のエネルギー。
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって。
負けそうになったら、
just cry out loud.
どうしても自らを見失って嫌いになって。
負けそうになったら、
just cry out loud.
傷つく音に、傷つく音に。
立ち向かう勇気へと導いてく our treasure。
裏切らないのは、最高に there is love。
かざしたちがい、光が生きるでしょう。
とても私の声が楽しい動画に伝えたんだ。
いいよ。
くてシかなategoris liquid味。
この技能は彼らで曲して伝うクルで。
最後に隠しさつのインスをつけたままね。
それが含まれれてくらいです。
このicianの状態を見れません。
そして、さったとき来いち方の暴動化をご覧やします。
Jealous? I bet you can't do any of that.
Impressive. I must say you are a true entertainer.
I've dreaded this day. I can't even juggle oranges.
You won't defeat me so easily.
I am the Wizard King, guardian of this nation and everyone in it.
Black Clover, page 93.
Julius Nova Crono.
All who stand before my time magic wither and fall.
Ridicıktor Recorded by Tommy
Issues of the Crono.